Guide to the David J. Skorton Presidential Liaison records, 2006-2014.
Skorton, David J. papers
- Series I. Meetings and Briefings
  - Lunch with Barbara and Stephen Friedman, March 2008 (Box 3)
  - Meeting with John Dyson, March 2008 (Box 3)
  - Meeting with Jules Kroll, March 2008 (Box 3)
  - Spring Recognition Event, March 2008 (Box 3)
  - Meeting with Jay and Eileen Walker, March 2008 (Box 3)
  - Meeting with Scott M. Smith, March 2008 (Box 3)
  - Meeting with Stephen and Evalyn Milman, March 2008 (Box 3)
  - Lunch with Roy Park Jr., March 2008 (Box 3)
  - Telephone conversation with Christopher Lee, April 2008 (Box 3)
  - Telephone call to Gara LaMarche, April 2008 (Box 3)
  - Dinner with Irwin and Joan Jacobs, April 2008 (Box 3)
  - Lunch meeting with David Duffield, April 2008 (Box 3)
  - Meeting with Ken Derr, April 2008 (Box 3)
  - Meeting with Jim and Becky Morgan; Dan Miller andRoger Strauch, April 2008 (Box 3)
  - Telephone call to Bob Appel, April 2008 (Box 3)
  - Meeting with CSV Advisors, April 2008 (Box 3)
  - CSV Annual Event, April 2008 (Box 3)
  - Meeting with Douglas Leone, April 2008 (Box 3)
  - Dinner hosted by Martha Coultrap (CAM), April 2008 (Box 3)
  - Lunch with Paul Gould, April 2008 (Box 3)
  - EPE Keynote Address, April 2008 (Box 3)
  - EPE Reception and Dinner, April 2008 (Box 3)
  - Meeting with Peter Kim (CAM), April 2008 (Box 3)
  - Campaign Reception at Susan Lynch’s home (CAM), April 2008 (Box 3)
  - Phone call to Lubna Olayan, April 2008 (Box 3)
  - Dinner hosted by David and Victoria Croll, April 2008 (Box 3)
  - Meeting with Todd Krasnow, April 2008 (Box 3)
  - Lunch meeting with Robert Langer, April 2008 (Box 3)
  - Meeting with Michael Zak, April 2008 (Box 3)
  - Meeting with Kevin McGovern, April 2008 (Box 3)
  - Lunch meeting with Robert Miller, April 2008 (Box 3)
  - Meeting with Harris Rosen, April 2008 (Box 3)
  - Parents Campus Visit Reception and Dinner, April 2008 (Box 3)
  - Parents Campus Visit Welcome, April 2008 (Box 3)
  - CUC Administrative Board Mtg, April 2008 (Box 3)
  - Lunch with Harlan Korenvaes and Rich Booth, April 2008 (Box 3)
  - Spring Tower Club Recognition, April 2008 (Box 3)
  - Meeting with Tom Jones, May 2008 (Box 3)
  - Lunch Meeting with Peter Robbins, May 2008 (Box 3)
  - Meeting with John Megrue, May 2008 (Box 3)
  - Johnson Museum Ground Breaking, May 2008 (Box 3)
  - Merrill Presidential Scholar Luncheon, May 2008 (Box 3)
  - Merrill Family Dinner, May 2008 (Box 3)
  - Meeting with Sherri Stuewer, May 2008 (Box 3)
  - Meeting with Fisk Johnson, May 2008 (Box 3)
  - Senior Class Campaign Reception, May 2008 (Box 3)
  - Meeting with Lubna Olayan, May 2008 (Box 3)
  - Trustee Reception and Dinner, May 2008 (Box 3)
  - Faculty Awards Dinner, May 2008 (Box 3)
  - Meeting with David Lederman, May 2008 (Box 3)
  - Dinner with Macaulay and Morgens, May 2008 (Box 3)
  - Phone call to Harris Rosen, June 2008 (Box 3)
  - Meeting with Allan R. Tessler, June 2008 (Box 3)
  - Class of 1948 Dinner, June 2008 (Box 3)
  - Classes of 1933, 1938, 1943 Reception, June 2008 (Box 3)
  - College of Veterinary Medicine, June 2008 (Box 3)
  - Phone call to Chuck Feeney, June 2008 (Box 3)
  - Class of 1953 Dinner, June 2008 (Box 3)
  - Class of 1958 Forum, June 2008 (Box 3)
  - Class of 1993 Dessert, June 2008 (Box 3)
  - Olin Lecture Lunch, June 2008 (Box 3)
  - Olin/Giving Reception, June 2008 (Box 6)
  - Olin Lecture, June 2008 (Box 3)
  - Class of 1983 Reception, June 2008 (Box 3)
  - Class of 1973 Dinner, June 2008 (Box 3)
  - State of the University Address, June 2008 (Box 3)
  - Class of 1963 Lunch, June 2008 (Box 3)
  - Class of 1988 Reception, June 2008 (Box 3)
  - Cornelliana Night, June 2008 (Box 3)
  - CUC Administrative Board Meeting (CAM), June 2008 (Box 3)
  - Tanner Award Luncheon for the Jacobs, June 2008 (Box 3)
  - Meeting with Al Kaneb, June 2008 (Box 3)
  - Lunch meeting with Seth Klarman, June 2008 (Box 3)
  - Dinner hosted by Harold and Nicki Tanner, June 2008 (Box 3)
  - Lunch with David Zalaznick, June 2008 (Box 3)
  - Meeting with Jules B. Kroll, June 2008 (Box 3)
  - Meeting with Robert Langer, June 2008 (Box 3)
  - Meeting with Gara LaMarche, June 2008 (Box 3)
  - Lunch with Gara LaMarche, June 2008 (Box 3)
  - Phone call to Jeff Parker, June 2008 (Box 3)
  - Janet Swanson Luncheon, July 4, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Legacy Breakfast, August 23, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Peter Eisenman, August 26, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with James and Ruth Clark, August 26, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Lunch meeting with Harold Tanner, September 3, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Jim Tisch, September 4, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Patty Harris, September 4, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Lunch meeting with David Fischell, September 4, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Reunion Kickoff Reception, September 5, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Reception and Dinner w/Cornell Commitment Students, September 6, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Presidential Councillors Annual Meeting: Rec. and Dinner hosted by President Emeritus, September 7, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Presidential Councillors Annual Meeting: Welcome, September 8, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Presidential Councillors Annual Meeting: Group Photo and Private Meeting w/PC’s, September 8, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Presidential Councillors Annual Meeting: Dinner w/President Skorton and Robin Davisson, September 8, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Alfred Spector, September 8, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Breakfast with Andrew Tisch, September 10, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Vincent McGee, September 11, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Sandy Weill, September 11, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Dinner with Harvey Dale and Debra LaMorte, September 12, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Larry Tanenbaum, September 12, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Jules Kroll, September 16, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Lunch meeting w/Ronay Menschel and Michele Moody-Adams, September 16, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Lunch meeting w/Gene Johnson and John Fitzpatrick, September 18, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Fisk Johnson, September 18, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Dinner and screening of The Lord God Bird documentary, September 18, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Roger Dower, September 18, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Lester Knight III, September 19, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with William D. Perez, September 19, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Lunch meeting with John and Jane Colman, September 19, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Atkinson Forum Dinner, September 20, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with David Atkinson, September 20, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Myra Maloney Hart FB Celebration, September 22, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Frank H. T. Rhodes Exemplary Service Awards, September 26, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Reception and luncheon honoring Andrew and Ann Tisch, September 26, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Applied Economics and Management (AEM) Advisory Council Meeting, September 26, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Lynch/Weiss Campus Visit, September 27, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Andy Boas, September 29, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Lunch meeting with Jay and Eileen Walker, October 3, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with David Zalaznick, October 3, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Seth Klarman, October 5, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Rec and Dinner with Irwin and Joan Jacobs and the Jacobs Scholars, October 6, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Breakfast with Irwin and Joan Jacobs, October 7, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Irene Rosenfeld, October 8, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Bill and Linda Macaulay, October 16, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Introducing Lubna S. Olayan: Keynote Speaker, October 16, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Fulfilling the Promise of Life Sciences: A Faculty Conversation, October 16, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Weill Dedication Celebration Dinner, October 16, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with John Swanson and Kent Fuchs, October 16, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Private Lunch with the Weill Family, October 16, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Weill Hall Dedication and Reception, October 16, 2008 (Box 4)
  - TCAM: Joint Annual Meeting / Conversation with David Skorton, October 17, 2008 (Box 4)
  - TCAM: Reception and Dinner, October 17, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Lubna Olayan and John Xefox, October 17, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Celebration of Scholarship, October 17, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Annual Fund Breakfast, October 18, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Cleveland Cornell Club 100th Anniversary Event, October 19, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Lunch meeting with Jeffrey Hawkins, October 22, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with David Duffield, October 22, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Amit Singhal and Sanjay Ghemawat, October 22, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Breakfast meeting with Anne Coors, October 23, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Vijay Vashee, October 23, 2008 (Box 4)
  - All Alumni Reception – Seattle WA, October 23, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Randy Tinseth, October 23, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Ronald McCray, October 23, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with David Thompson, October 23, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Luncheon with Microsoft Cornellians, October 23, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Chuck Knight, October 28, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Mississippi River Cornell Adult University trip, October 29, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Reception and Dinner with Appel Fellows, November 6, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Lab of Ornithology Reception and Dinner, November 7, 2008 (Box 4)
  - San Jose CA Pre-Campaign Event (Harris), November 5, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Lunch meeting with H. Laurance and Nancy Fuller, November 6, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Judith Biggs Dedication, November 10, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Dinner with Stephen Friedman, November 11, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Glenn August, November 12, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Lunch meeting with Peter Robbins, November 12, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Barbara Novick, November 12, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Dinner hosted by Deedie and Rusty Rose, November 24, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Lunch meeting with Harlan Korenvaes, November 24, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Foremost Benefactor Lunch for Don Opatrny, December 1, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with John Dyson, December 8, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Allan Tessler, December 8, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with John McAuliffe, December 8, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Breakfast meeting with Andrew Boas, December 10, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Ratan Tata, December 17, 2008 (Box 4)
  - International Conference “Development, Freedom and Welfare” in honor of Prof. Amartya Sen, December 19, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Narayana Murthy, December 22, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Telephone call with Dr. W. Robert Connor, January 9, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Dr. Fred Dombrose, January 12, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Major Gifts Committee Meeting (FUCHS), January 21, 2009 (Box 4)
  - President’s Circle Dinner, January 21, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Class of 1979 Reunion Warm-Up Reception (FUCHS), January 25, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Lunch with Becky and Jim Morgan (FUCHS), January 27, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Katrina James, January 27, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Phone call with David Litman, February 5, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Phone call to Michael J. Petrillose, February 5, 2009 (Box 4)
  - CACO Luncheon, February 7, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with L. William Kay, February 7, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Lawrence Salameno, February 12, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Lunch meeting with Franci Blassberg, February 12, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Michael Schulhof, February 12, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Bob Katz, February 13, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Lunch with Steven and Evalyn Milman, February 13, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Johnson Museum Spring Exhibition Rec and Dinner, February 13, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Doug Braunstein, February 13, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Craig Klosk, February 13, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Alfred Spector, February 13, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Senior Class Kickoff Reception, February 16, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Dinner hosted by Alan and Betsey Harris, February 18, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Lunch hosted by Lee and Mary Pillsbury, February 19, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Chuck Knight, February 20, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Breakfast with Dick Loynd, February 20, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Armando Olivera, February 20, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Lunch meeting with Howard Milstein, February 20, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Cornell Group Dinner, February 20, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Dinner hosted by Bob and Helen Appel, February 20, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Investment Committee Meeting, February 21, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Phone conversation with Roger Dower, February 24, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Dinner with Seth Klarman, February 25, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Ruben King-Shaw, February 25, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Breakfast meeting with Al Kaneb, February 26, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with David Croll, February 26, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Reception and Dinner hosted by David and Joan Rosenberg, February 26, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Ed Fox, February 26, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Croll Professor of Sustainable Energy Systems (FUCHS), March 4, 2009 (Box 4)
  - President’s Council on Cornell Women (PCCW) Reception and Dinner, March 6, 2009 (Box 4)
  - PCCW Senior Administration Update (FUCHS), March 6, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Sanjay Ghemawat, March 11, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Jonathan Rubinstein, March 11, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Jeffrey Hawkins, March 11, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Neal Douglas, March 11, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Cornell Silicon Valley Plus Dinner, March 11, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Cornell Silicon Valley 10 Event, March 12, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Robert Shaw, March 12, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Michael Goguen, March 12, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Kenneth Brown, March 12, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Lunch meeting with Tom Dinwoodie, March 12, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Breakfast meeting with Amit Singhal, March 13, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Computing and Information Science Advisory Board Meeting, March 13, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Dinner and Concert with Irwin and Joan Jacobs, March 13, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Dinner hosted by Don Miller, March 18, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Gara LaMarche, March 19, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Dinner with David and Sarah Fischell, March 19, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Jules Kroll, March 19, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with George Gellert, March 20, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Charles Lee, March 20, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Breakfast with Harris Rosen, March 31, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Arts and Sciences Advisory Council Meeting (FUCHS), April 3, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Washington DC Campaign Celebration, April 3, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Lunch with Edward Meyer and Andrew Tisch, April 7, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Ira Drukier, April 7, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Paul Gould, April 7, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Lunch with Roy Park, April 13, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Roger Dower, April 14, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Andrew and Virginia Rudd, April 15, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Harris Rosen, April 16, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Kevin McGovern Dedication, April 16, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Jay Walker, April 17, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Atkinson Forum Dinner, April 21, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Frank Holland, April 22, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Coffee with Charlie Lynch, April 22, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Dyson Scholars Program Lunch (FUCHS), April 23, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Mann Library Terrace Dedication – John Dyson (FUCHS), April 23, 2009 (Box 4)
  - CALS Advisory Council Meeting (FUCHS), April 23, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Rob and Peter Dyson, April 23, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Breakfast meeting with David and Pat Atkinson (FUCHS), April 23, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Parents Campus Visit: Welcome, April 24, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Parents Campus Visit: Dinner (FUCHS), April 24, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Dinner hosted by Lubna Olayan and John Xefox, April 28, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Lunch with Robert LeBlanc, May 1, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Michael Borkan, May 1, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Tea with Chris Bergmann, May 1, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Lubna Olayan, May 1, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Dinner hosted by Douglas Henderson, May 1, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Merrill Family Sailing Center Dedication (FUCHS), May 9, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Peter Bruns, May 11, 2009 (Box 4)
  - New York City Tower Club Reception, May 14, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Senior Class Campaign Final Reception, May 22, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Trustee Reception and Dinner, May 22, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Board of Trustees Faculty Recognition Dinner, May 23, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Foremost Benefactor Photo and Statue Presentation: Irwin and Joan Jacobs, May 24, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Foremost Benefactor Plaque presentation – Thomas Gill (FUCHS), May 24, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Dinner with Ratan Tata, May 27, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Lunch meeting with Nandlal Tolani, May 28, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Larry Fuller (FUCHS), May 29, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Classes of 1934, 1939 and 1944 combined reception, June 2, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Franci Blassberg (DAVISSON), June 2, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Robert Ziff, June 3, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Dinner with Fisk Johnson and Ratan Tata, June 3, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Bob Harrison, June 3, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Lunch meeting with Merryl Tisch, June 3, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Sam and Diane Bodman, June 4, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Ratan Tata Film Screening/Reception, June 4, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Bill Vanneman’s 100th Birthday Party, June 4, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Class of 1974 35th Reunion Town Hall Meeting, June 5, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Class of 1964 Reception, June 5, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Class of 1979 Dinner, June 5, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Class of 1989 Dessert, June 5, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Allan Tessler, June 5, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Olin Giving Society Reception (FUCHS), June 5, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Breakfast with Ratan Tata (FUCHS), June 5, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Class of 1959 Romping and Stomping (DAVISSON), June 5, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Don Opatrny (FUCHS), June 5, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Luncheon with Olin Lecture Speaker, Ratan Tata, June 5, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Olin Lecture, June 5, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Cornell Native American Alumni Association (CNAAA) Iroquois Social, June 6, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Class of 1954 55th Reunion Luncheon, June 6, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Class of 1949 60th Reunion Reception, June 6, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Class of 1984 25th Reunion Reception, June 6, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Class of 1959 50th Reunion Reception, June 6, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Cornelliana Night, June 6, 2009 (Box 4)
  - State of the University Address, June 6, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Lunch with Bob and Marilyn Abrams, June 9, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Barbara and Steve Friedman, June 9, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Leonard Litwin, June 9, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Ronay Menschel, June 9, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Sherri Stuewer, June 11, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Meeting with Neal Douglas (FUCHS), June 16, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Phone call to Roger Dower, June 26, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Lubna Olayan Phone Call, July 26, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Phone call to Roger Dower, July 29, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Phone call to Fisk Johnson, July 30, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Meeting with David Duffield (FUCHS), August 11, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Meeting with Ann Bowers (FUCHS), August 12, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Lunch meeting with Michael Goguen (FUCHS), August 12, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Meeting with Douglas Leone (FUCHS), August 12, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Meeting with Jon Rubinstein (FUCHS), August 12, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Dinner with Jim and Becky Morgan (FUCHS), August 12, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Meeting with Andrew Verhalen (FUCHS), August 12, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Dinner with Irwin and Joan Jacobs (FUCHS), August 13, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Meeting with Fred Kavli and Miyoung Chun (FUCHS), August 13, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Meeting with Lee Asseo (FUCHS), August 13, 2009 (Box 5)
  - John and Elaine Alexanders Foremost Benefactor Ceremony and Lunch, August 17, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Meeting with Nandlal and Papu Tolani, August 17, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Meeting with Chris Marshall, August 20, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Meeting with Bob and Laura Langer, August 21, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Legacy Reception, August 22, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Meeting with Fred Young, September 3, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Phone call to Andy Paul, September 4, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Presidential Councillors Annual Meeting (PCAM): President Emeriti Rec and Dinner, September 13, 2009 (Box 5)
  - PCAM: Reception and Dinner w/David J. Skorton and Robin L. Davisson, September 14, 2009 (Box 5)
  - PCAM: Welcome, September 14, 2009 (Box 5)
  - PCAM: Group Photo and Private Meeting, September 14, 2009 (Box 5)
  - PCAM: Reimaging Cornell (FUCHS), September 14, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Breakfast meeting with Allan Tessler, September 14, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Meeting with Hank Bartels (FUCHS), September 15, 2009 (Box 5)
  - AAandD Fall Kickoff Meeting, September 21, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Dinner hosted by Don and Muffy Miller, September 22, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Phone call to Jeffrey Lehman, September 26, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Lunch meeting with Robert and Laura Langer, September 30, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Dinner with David and Pat Atkinson (FUCHS), October 1, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Lunch meeting with David Atkinson (FUCHS), October 2, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Breakfast with Andrew and Ann Tisch, October 2, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Atkinson Dinner, October 2, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Neil Rubler and Eric Feuerstein, October 7, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Meeting with Ronay Menschel, October 7, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Lunch with James and Merryl Tisch, October 8, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Meeting with John Dyson, October 8, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Meeting with Charles Knight (FUCHS), October 8, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Lunch with Phil and Shelly Proujansky, October 15, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Meeting with Jonathan and Lizzie Tisch, October 15, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Frank H. T .Rhodes Exemplary Alumni Service Awards Reception and Dinner, October 16, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Meeting with David Fischell, October 16, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Cornell Association of Class Officers (CACO) and Cornell Alumni Association Board Meeting, October 17, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Lynch/Weiss Welcome, October 17, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Lynch/Weiss Luncheon, October 17, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Hatfield Lecture, October 22, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Keynote Address by W. Kent Fuchs, October 22, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Dinner with Fisk Johnson and Pete Meinig, October 22, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Screening of “Carnaub, A Son’s Memoir”, October 22, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Meeting with Fisk Johnson, October 22, 2009 (Box 5)
  - A Celebration of Scholarship, October 23, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Dinner – Setting the Pace: 1865-2015, October 23, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Joint Annual Meeting, October 23, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Cornell Annual Fund Breakfast, October 24, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Meeting with John Swanson (FUCHS), October 26, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Foremost Benefactor Ceremony: Bob and Anne Shaw (FUCHS), October 29, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Meeting with Craig Wheeler (FUCHS), November 2, 2009 (Box 5)
  - All-Alumni Event – Seoul, November 4, 2009 (Box 5)
  - All-Alumni Event – Bejing, November 7, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Meeting with Dr. Fred Dombrose (FUCHS), November 11, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Andrew and Margaret Paul Foremost Benefactor Ceremony and Lunch, November 13, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Lab of Ornithology Reception, November 13, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Meeting with Howard Milstein, November 18, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Dinner hosted by Peter Joseph and Elizabeth Scheuer, November 19, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Teagle Board Luncheon, November 20, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Phone call to Harris Rosen, November 9, 2013 (Box 5)
  - Pre-game Tailgate, Cornell University vs. Boston Hockey game, November 28, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Phone meeting with Jim Morgan (FUCHS), December 4, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Lunch meeting with Seth Klarman, December 7, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Meeting with Robert Langer and Desh Deshpande, December 7, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Meeting with Al Kaneb, December 7, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Dinner with David Lederman, December 7, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Breakfast with Stephen and Nancy Einhorn (FUCHS), December 11, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Meeting with Peter Robbins, December 11, 2009 (Box 5)
  - Major Gifts Committee Meeting, January 20, 2010 (Box 5)
  - President’s Circle Dinner, January 20, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Meeting with Harvey Dale (FUCHS), January 20, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Meeting with Ratan Tata, January 22, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Meeting with Patti Harris, January 25, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Phone call to Harris Rosen, January 29, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Cornell Alumni Leadership Conference Luncheon (FUCHS), January 30, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Senior Class Campaign Kickoff, February 1, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Lunch meeting with Roy Park and Joanne Florino (FUCHS), February 4, 2010 (Box 5)